- I don't understand...
- Bup, bup, bup.
- Okay, but earlier it seemed like...
- No talking.
(Leonard:)Even during?
Because sometimes I have questions.
(Penny:)Well, that was fun.
(Leonard:)Yeah. Except for when
I got the foot cramp.
(Penny:)You hung in there though.
(Leonard:)There was a lot at stake.
So, what do you wanna do now?
Well, I wanna go get my asthma inhaler,
but it might ruin the moment.
So help me out, here.
How does a miserable date end in sex?
(Penny:)I don't know, it's complicated.
I'm pretty smart guy, and right now my
brain has dibs on the blood supply...
(Leonard:)...so give it a go.
(Penny:)Okay. It's just...
At that restaurant when you said
you wanted us to be together again...